Guide to the Charles Seymour, President of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence and subject files, 1917-1954 1937-1950; 1937-1950; Series I
  - Childs, Jane Coffin, Memorial Fund for Medical Research: minutes, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 344)
  - Chiliastri and Pastro case
    See: box 126, folder 1066
  - Chinese broadcast, 1943-1945 (Box 40, Folder 345)
  - Chinese Cultural Scholarships, 1944-1946 (Box 40, Folder 346)
  - Christian Conference: Yale preaching mission, 1938-1945 (Box 40, Folder 347)
  - Citizens' Committee for Universal Military Training for Young Men
    See: box 138, folder 1166
  - Citizens' Military Training Camps (CMTC) Scholarships
    See: box 33, folder 285
  - Civil Aeronautics Authority Program, 1939-1944 (Box 40, Folder 348)
  - Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC)
    See: box 33, folder 286
  - Cl, 1938-1950 (Box 40, Folder 349)
  - Cl, 1938-1950 (Box 41, Folder 350)
  - Clare Fellowship (Paul Mellon), 1938-1950 (Box 41, Folder 351)
  - Class Gift Fund, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 352)
  - Class Reunion Bureau, 1938-1948 (Box 41, Folder 353)
  - Class Schedules, Committee to Administer the Uniform System of, 1945-1948 (Box 41, Folder 354)
  - Class Secretaries, Yale Association of, 1937-1950 (Box 41, Folder 355)
  - Classes, dinners, records, etc., 1937-1950 (Box 41, Folder 356)
  - Classes, dinners, records, etc., 1937-1950 (Box 42, Folder 357-360)
  - Classics, Department of, 1939-1949 (Box 42, Folder 361)
  - Clellan Ford Project, 1948-1950 (Box 42, Folder 362)
  - Clinic of Child Development
    See: box 133, folder 1118-1120
  - Co, 1937-1950 (Box 42, Folder 363)
  - Coe, William R. Collection, 1939-1950 (Box 43, Folder 364-365)
  - Coffin, Charles A, Memorial Fund
    See: box 108, folder 916
  - Coffin, Henry Sloane, 1938-1950 (Box 43, Folder 366)
  - Col - Com, 1937-1950 (Box 43, Folder 367-368)
  - Coleman, Mrs. William H., 1939-1950 (Box 44, Folder 369)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1942-1949 (Box 44, Folder 370)
  - College Funds Committee
    See: box 156, folder 1317
  - College, Yale, 1937-1949 (Box 44, Folder 371-373)
  - College, Yale: conference group, 1937 (Box 44, Folder 374)
  - College, Yale: course of study, 1941-1949 (Box 44, Folder 375)
  - College, Yale: Dean, William C.Devane, 1937-1948 (Box 44, Folder 376)
  - College, Yale: Deanship, 1937-1948 (Box 44, Folder 377)
  - College, Yale: grading system, 1939-1942 (Box 44, Folder 378)
  - College, Yale: special committee to consider the chair of Biblical Literature, 1942 (Box 44, Folder 379)
  - Columbia University, 1937-1950 (Box 45, Folder 380-381)
  - Columbia University: initiatory university group, national nuclear science lab. (Northeastern), 1946-1950 (Box 45, Folder 382)
  - Commencement, 1938-1949 (Box 45, Folder 383-384)
  - Commencement: alumni luncheon, 1938 (Box 45, Folder 385)
  - Commencement: baccalaureate, 1938 (Box 45, Folder 386)
  - Commencement: graduation, 1938 (Box 45, Folder 387)
  - Commencement, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 388)
  - Commencement: alumni luncheon, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 389)
  - Commencement: baccalaureate, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 390)
  - Commencement: graduation, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 391)
  - Commencement, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 392)
  - Commencement: alumni luncheon, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 393)
  - Commencement: baccalaureate, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 394)
  - Commencement: graduation, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 395)
  - Commencement, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 396-396a)
  - Commencement: alumni luncheon, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 397)
  - Commencement: baccalaureate, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 398)
  - Commencement: graduation, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 399)
  - Commencement, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 400)
  - Commencement: alumni luncheon, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 401)
  - Commencement: baccalaureate, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 402)
  - Commencement: graduation, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 403)
  - Commencement: graduation, baccalaureate, class dinner, class day; War class, 1942 December 18-19 (Box 47, Folder 404)
  - Commencement, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 405)
  - Commencement: valedictory dinner, 1943 October (Box 47, Folder 406)
  - Commencement, 1944 June 22 (Box 47, Folder 407)
  - Commencement: valedictory dinner, 1944 October 19 (Box 47, Folder 408)
  - Commencement, 1945 June 22 (Box 47, Folder 409)
  - Commencement: 1945 class day exercises, 1945 February 1 (Box 47, Folder 410)
  - Commencement: graduation, 1945 February 23 (Box 47, Folder 411)
  - Commencement: graduation, 1945 October 24 (Box 47, Folder 412)
  - Commencement, 1946 June 25 (Box 48, Folder 413)
  - Commencement: alumni luncheon, 1945 June 25 (Box 48, Folder 414)
  - Commencement: graduation, 1946 February 22 (Box 48, Folder 415)
  - Commencement: memorial service, 1946 June 23 (Box 48, Folder 416)
  - Commencement, 1947 June 18 (Box 48, Folder 417)
  - Commencement: alumni luncheon, 1947 June 18 (Box 48, Folder 418)
  - Commencement: baccalaureate, 1947 June 15 (Box 48, Folder 419)
  - Commencement: graduation, 1947 June 16 (Box 48, Folder 420)
  - Commencement, 1948 June 22 (Box 48, Folder 421)
  - Commencement: alumni luncheon, 1948 June 22 (Box 48, Folder 422)
  - Commencement: baccalaureate, 1948 June 20 (Box 48, Folder 423)
  - Commencement: graduation, 1948 February 6 (Box 48, Folder 424)
  - Commencement: graduation, 1948 June 21 (Box 48, Folder 425)
  - Commencement, 1949 June 21 (Box 48, Folder 426)
  - Commencement: alumni luncheon, 1949 June 21 (Box 49, Folder 427)
  - Commencement: baccalaureate, 1949 June 19 (Box 49, Folder 428)
  - Commencement: graduation, 1949 February 5 (Box 49, Folder 429)
  - Commencement: graduation, 1949 June 20 (Box 49, Folder 430)
  - Commencement, 1950 June 12 (Box 49, Folder 431)
  - Commencement: alumni meeting, 1950 June 19 (Box 49, Folder 432)
  - Commencement: baccalaureate, 1950 June 11 (Box 49, Folder 433)
  - Commencement: general, class day, reunion, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 434)
  - Commonwealth Fund: fellowships, 1942-1948 (Box 49, Folder 435)
  - Communists, 1940-1950 (Box 49, Folder 436-437)
  - Community Council
    See: box 173, folder 1490
  - Community Relations Committee
    See: box 177, folder 1532
  - Con - Cop, 1937-1950 (Box 50, Folder 438-441)
  - Con - Cop, 1937-1950 (Box 51, Folder 442-443)
  - Connecticut Council on Higher Education, 1947-1949 (Box 51, Folder 444)
  - Connecticut Geological and Natural History Survey, 1937-1946 (Box 51, Folder 445-446)
  - Connecticut, Governor: Chester A. Bowles, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 447)
  - Connecticut Interracial Commission: racial discrimination, anti-discrimination bill, 1945-1949 (Box 51, Folder 448)
  - Connecticut Post-War Planning Board: interim report, "Postwar Connecticut", 1944 August (Box 52, Folder 449)
  - Connecticut Society of the Cincinnati, 1937-1946 (Box 52, Folder 450)
  - Connecticut State Department of Education, 1937-1950 (Box 52, Folder 451)
  - Connfelt, Mr and Mrs O.G., 1940-1944 (Box 52, Folder 452)
  - Conservation, Department of: professor of conservation, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 453)
  - Convocation, 1946 October 18-19 (Box 52, Folder 454)
  - Copyright, International, 1937 (Box 52, Folder 455)
  - Cor - Coy, 1937-1950 (Box 53, Folder 456-457)
  - Corporation: assignment of members to special fields of interest, 1939-1942 (Box 53, Folder 458)
  - Corporation: Buckner Committee on Operating Costs; Buckner, chairman, Schley, Loomis, 1936-1937 (Box 53, Folder 459)
  - Corporation: by-laws, 1938-1950 (Box 53, Folder 460)
  - Corporation: by-laws, revision of, 1937-1938 (Box 53, Folder 461)
  - Corporation: Committee of Survey in Connection with Selection of Next President, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 462)
  - Corporation: Committee on Architectural Plan, 1937-1950 (Box 53, Folder 463)
  - Corporation: Committee on Architectural Plan: minutes, 1938-1950 (Box 53, Folder 464)
  - Corporation: Committee on Buildings and Grounds, 1939-1941 (Box 53, Folder 465)
  - Corporation: Committee on Corporation Meetings, 1937 (Box 53, Folder 466)
  - Corporation: Committee on Educational Policy: materials, 1945 (Box 54, Folder 467)
  - Corporation: Committee on Educational Policy: meetings, 1937-1950 (Box 54, Folder 468)
  - Corporation: Committee on Educational Policy: minutes, 1937-1950 (Box 54, Folder 469)
  - Corporation: Committee on Law School, 1937-1949 (Box 54, Folder 470)
  - Corporation: Committee on Library and Museums, 1938-1950 (Box 54, Folder 471)
  - Corporation: Committee on Retiring Allowances, 1938 (Box 54, Folder 472)
  - Corporation: Committee on War Memorials, 1945-1949 (Box 54, Folder 473)
  - Corporation: Committee to Report upon the Administrative Organization of the University, 1939 (Box 54, Folder 474)
  - Corporation: committees and members, 1937-1950 (Box 54, Folder 475)
  - Corporation: Finance Committee, 1937-1949 (Box 54, Folder 476)
  - Corporation: Prudential Committee: general, 1937-1950 (Box 54, Folder 477)
  - Corporation: Prudential Committee: general, 1937-1950 (Box 55, Folder 478-480)
  - Corporation: gowns, 1938 (Box 55, Folder 481)
  - Corporation: memorandum for the "Opportunities of the Colleges Plan for Educational Supervision", undated (Box 55, Folder 482)
  - Corporation: memorandum re. budget, 1937 October 22 (Box 55, Folder 483)
  - Corporation: Prudential Committee: minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 55, Folder 484)
  - Corporation: miscellaneous, 1949 (Box 55, Folder 485)
  - Corporation: Mr. Seymour"s dinner for members and ex-members, 1938 May 14 (Box 55, Folder 486)
  - Corporation: President"s report re. balancing future budgets, 1948 (Box 55, Folder 487)
  - Corporation: Prudential Committee: re. Medical School endowment, undated (Box 55, Folder 488)
  - Corporation, report to the: Limitation of the Size of the Undergraduate Class, 1938 (Box 56, Folder 489)
  - Corporation: Special Committee to Assist the Officers with Budgets, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 490)
  - Corporation: successors to the original trustees, 1938-1947 (Box 56, Folder 491)
  - Correspondence: personal, 1942-1950 (Box 56, Folder 492)
  - Costs of higher education, 1948-1950 (Box 56, Folder 493-495)
  - Cot, Pierre, 1941-1944 (Box 57, Folder 496)
  - Council of Masters
    See: box 156, folder 1311-1312 See: box 200, folder 1-6 See: box 201, folder 7-10
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1937-1950 (Box 57, Folder 497)
  - Council on Library and Museums
    See: box 98, folder 840
  - Cowles Foundation, 1937 (Box 57, Folder 498)
  - Coxe, Mrs. Alexander Brown, 1937-1941 (Box 57, Folder 499)
  - Cr, 1939-1949 (Box 57, Folder 500)
  - Cranks, 1950 (Box 57, Folder 501)
  - Crosby, Sumner McKnight
    See: box 7, folder 55
  - Cu, 1937-1950 (Box 57, Folder 502)
  - Cushing, Harvey and Cushing Library Advisory Board
    See: box 108, folder 917-918
  - D, 1940-1950 (Box 57, Folder 503)
  - Darling, George B.
    See: box 108, folder 922
  - Dartmouth College, 1937-1949 (Box 57, Folder 504)
  - Dav, 1937-1950 (Box 57, Folder 505)
  - Davenport College
    See: box 157, folder 1322
  - Davis, Jerome, 1927-1938 (Box 58, Folder 506-507)
  - Davis, Jerome: Corporation correspondence, 1937 (Box 58, Folder 508)
  - Davison, F. Trubee, 1938-1948 (Box 58, Folder 509)
  - Day, George Parmly, 1938-1949 (Box 58, Folder 510)
  - De, 1937-1949 (Box 58, Folder 511)
  - Deans, 1939-1950 (Box 59, Folder 512)
  - Deans: Compulsory Accident Insurance Plan, 1941 (Box 59, Folder 513)
  - Debating Association, Yale, 1938-1950 (Box 59, Folder 514)
  - Degrees: votes regarding, 1939-1949 (Box 59, Folder 515)
  - Den, 1938-1949 (Box 59, Folder 516)
  - Denison, Ellen H. and Charles L., 1939 (Box 59, Folder 517)
  - Departmental Chairmen, 1936-1950 (Box 59, Folder 518)
  - Devane, William C.
    See: box 44, folder 376
  - Development Committee
    See: box 129, folder 1092
  - The Development of the Sciences, 1947 (Box 59, Folder 519)
  - Di, 1937-1950 (Box 59, Folder 520)
  - Dickey, Charles D., 1946-1950 (Box 59, Folder 521)
  - Dining Hall, 1937-1948 (Box 59, Folder 522)
  - Dining Halls
    See: box 157, folder 1326
  - Directories
    See: box 157, folder 1327
  - Divinity School, 1937-1950 (Box 60, Folder 523-527)
  - Divinity School: deanship, 1948 (Box 61, Folder 528)
  - Do, 1937-1949 (Box 61, Folder 529)
  - Dodge, Marshall Jr.
    See: box 6, folder 52
  - Dramatic Art, Department of, 1937-1950 (Box 61, Folder 530-531)
  - Dramatic Art, Department of: Allardyce Nicoll, 1940-1945 (Box 61, Folder 532)
  - Dramatic Association, 1937-1950 (Box 61, Folder 533)
  - Drier, Miss Katherine S., 1941-1950 (Box 61, Folder 534)
  - Du, 1937-1950 (Box 62, Folder 535)
  - Dupont Fellowship in Chemistry, 1937-1950 (Box 62, Folder 536)
  - Dura - Europos, 1937-1948 (Box 62, Folder 537)
  - Dwight Hall
    See: box 181, folder 1557-1559
  - Dwight, Timothy College
    See: box 157, folder 1328
  - E, 1938-1949 (Box 62, Folder 538)
  - Eastern Association of College Deans and Advisors of Men, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 539)
  - Economics, Department of, 1938-1950 (Box 62, Folder 540-541)
  - Economics, Department of, 1938-1950 (Box 63, Folder 542)
  - Education, Department of: Adult Education Program, 1945 (Box 63, Folder 543)
  - Education, Department of: report to the President, 1930-1950 (Box 63, Folder 543a)
  - Educational Aptitude Testing Program
    See: box 33, folder 289
  - Educational Costs Committee
    See: box 175, folder 1509 See: box 75, folder 664a
  - Educational Planning Committee
    See: box 175, folder 1510-1511
    See: box 176, folder 1512
  - Educational Policy Committee
    See: box 54, folder 467-469
  - Edwards, Jonathan College
    See: box 155, folder 1302
  - Efron, Mr and Mrs. Andrew (Julia), 1940-1941 (Box 63, Folder 544)
  - Eg, 1937-1950 (Box 63, Folder 545)
  - Elizabethan Club, 1947, 1950 (Box 63, Folder 546)
  - Em, 1937-1950 (Box 63, Folder 547)
  - Emerson, Thomas
    See: box 94, folder 809
  - Endowment and Gifts Committee
  - Endowment Fund, 1926, 1938 (Box 63, Folder 548)
  - Engineering: "Memorandum on Opportunities and Needs in Internal Combustion and Automotive Engineering", 1940 February (Box 63, Folder 548a)
  - Engineering Association, 1937-1950 (Box 63, Folder 549-550)
  - Engineering Association, 1937-1950 (Box 64, Folder 551-553)
  - Engineering Committee
    See: box 163, folder 1385
  - Engineering Education, Society for the Promotion of, 1939-1949 (Box 64, Folder 554)
  - Engineering School, 1937-1950 (Box 64, Folder 555)
  - Engineering School: Chemical Engineering Department, 1939-1950 (Box 64, Folder 556)
  - Engineering School: Civil Engineering, 1938-1949 (Box 64, Folder 557)
  - Engineering School: Committee on Engineering, 1945-1947 (Box 65, Folder 558)
  - Engineering School: Electrical Engineering, 1938-1949 (Box 65, Folder 559)
  - Engineering School: Electrical Engineering: new wing Dunham Laboratory, 1944 (Box 65, Folder 560)
  - Engineering School: Engineering Drawing, Department of, 1939, 1943 (Box 65, Folder 561)
  - Engineering School: Engineering Mechanics, 1937-1940 (Box 65, Folder 562)
  - Engineering School: Industrial Administration (previously Industrial Engineering), 1948-1950 (Box 65, Folder 563)
  - Engineering School: Mechanical Engineering, Department of, 1938-1950 (Box 65, Folder 564)
  - Engineering School: Metallurgy, Department of (formerly Department of Mining & Metallurgy), 1937-1950 (Box 65, Folder 565)
  - Engineering School: minutes, 1946-1950 (Box 65, Folder 566)
  - Engineering School: program for development in chemical engineering, 1940-1947 (Box 65, Folder 567)
  - Engineering School: Westinghouse Educational Foundation (Fellowship in Electrical Engineering), 1946-1949 (Box 65, Folder 568)
  - Engineers' Council for Professional Development, 1937-1946 (Box 66, Folder 569)
  - English, Department of, 1937-1949 (Box 66, Folder 570)
  - Eno Foundation (For Highway Traffic Control Inc.), 1938-1948 (Box 66, Folder 571-573)
  - Eno Foundation (For Highway Traffic Control Inc.), 1938-1948 (Box 67, Folder 574)
  - Enrollment and Scholarship Committee
    See: box 176, folder 1514
  - Entertainment Committee
    See: box 130, folder 1100
  - Er, 1938-1949 (Box 67, Folder 575)
  - Estate taxes and charitable legacies, 1939-1941 (Box 67, Folder 576)
  - Examination fee system (common), 1939-1950 (Box 67, Folder 577)
  - Experimental Program, 1945-1948 (Box 67, Folder 578)
  - F, 1938-1950 (Box 68, Folder 579-580)
  - Faculty, 1937-1950 (Box 68, Folder 581)
  - Faculty: Committee on the Distribution of Class Hours (Mr. Havemeyer), 1946 (Box 68, Folder 582)
  - Faculty: four course plan, 1938-1948 (Box 68, Folder 583)
  - Faculty: Interdepartmental Committee to Study the Question of coordinating Programs in Clinical Psychology, 1949-1950 (Box 68, Folder 584)
  - Faculty: scholarship aid for sons, 1937-1941 (Box 68, Folder 585)
  - Faculty Club, 1929-1948 (Box 68, Folder 586)
  - Faculty Forum (proposed) (Mr. Schoolcraft), 1941 (Box 68, Folder 587)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1938-1948 (Box 68, Folder 588)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences: committee on schedules, 1938-1946 (Box 68, Folder 589)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences: committee on scholarships, 1939-1942 (Box 68, Folder 590)
    See also: box 34, folder 301
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences: executive committee, 1935-1950 (Box 68, Folder 591)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences: minutes, 1938-1940, 1947 (Box 68, Folder 592)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences: policy governing appointment and tenure, 1939-1947 (Box 68, Folder 593)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences: salary correspondence, 1945 (Box 69, Folder 594)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences: salary, instructors (professional school), 1945-1946 (Box 69, Folder 595)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences: salary scale, 1945 (Box 69, Folder 596)
  - Far Eastern Languages, Institute of
    See: box 86, folder 751
  - Far Eastern Studies Program, 1937-1946 (Box 69, Folder 597)
    See also: box 86, folder 749
  - Farmer, Malcolm
    See: box 22, folder 181
  - Farnam, Thomas W., 1937-1944 (Box 69, Folder 598)
  - Farnell, Albert D.
    See: box 5, folder 40
  - Fates, Harold Leighton
    See: box 7, folder 56
  - Fe, 1937-1949 (Box 69, Folder 599)
  - Fi, 1937-1950 (Box 69, Folder 600)
  - Finance Committee
    See: box 54, folder 476
  - Financial Aid Requirements
    See: box 147, folder 1239
  - Fisher, H.B., 1941-1943 (Box 70, Folder 601)
  - Fisher, Samuel H., 1937-1949 (Box 70, Folder 602)
  - Fl - Fo, 1937-1950 (Box 70, Folder 603-605)
  - Focillon, Prof and Mrs. Henri
    See: box 17, folder 149
  - Ford, Clellan S.
    See: box 42, folder 362
  - Foreign Area and Language Studies Committee
    See: box 129, folder 1089
  - Foreign Area Studies, 1942-1950 (Box 70, Folder 606)
  - Foreign Language Teaching Committee
    See: box 129, folder 1090 See: box 130, folder 1101
  - Foreign Service Educational Foundation, 1944, 1948-1949 (Box 71, Folder 607)
  - Forestry School, 1937-1950 (Box 71, Folder 608-609)
  - Forestry School: Committee on School Forests, 1939-1942 (Box 71, Folder 610)
  - Forestry School: Dean, Henry S. Graves, 1938-1945 (Box 71, Folder 611)
  - Forestry School: natural preserve, 1939-1950 (Box 71, Folder 612)
  - Forestry School: northeastern forest experiment station, 1937-1942 (Box 71, Folder 613)
  - Forty Two Club ('42), 1945-1949 (Box 71, Folder 614)
  - Four Course Plan
    See: box 68, folder 583
  - Fowler Association, 1938-1945 (Box 71, Folder 615)
  - Fr, 1937-1950 (Box 71, Folder 616)
  - Fr, 1937-1950 (Box 72, Folder 617)
  - Fraternities, 1940-1950 (Box 72, Folder 618)
  - Fraternity/College Relations
    See: box 156, folder 1320
  - French, Department of, 1937-1950 (Box 72, Folder 619-620)
  - French, Department of: Yale-Reid Hall summer session, 1950 (Box 72, Folder 621)
  - French, Robert Dudley
  - Freshman Year, 1937-1950 (Box 72, Folder 622-624)
  - Freshman Year: assembly, 1939-1949 (Box 73, Folder 625)
  - Freshman Year: athletic program, 1938-1950 (Box 73, Folder 626)
  - Freshman Year: Buck-Acheson Committee re: limitation in the number of freshmen admitted, 1937-1938 (Box 73, Folder 627)
  - Freshman Year: building needs, 1946 (Box 73, Folder 628)
  - Freshman Year: counsellor system, 1938-1947 (Box 73, Folder 629)
  - Freshman Year: deanship, 1937 (Box 73, Folder 630)
  - Freshman Year: dormitory assignments (moving of freshmen because of agreement with government), 1941 (Box 73, Folder 631)
  - Freshman Year: housing (problems of moving the offices onto the old campus), 1938 (Box 73, Folder 632)
  - Freshman Year: increased enrollment and scholarship situation 1941-1942
    See: box 33, folder 293
  - Freshman Year: minutes, 1938-1950 (Box 73, Folder 633)
  - Freshman Year: New York Yale Club freshman prizes, 1937-1949 (Box 73, Folder 634)
  - Freshman Year: problems (including a report to the Corporation), 1937-1938 (Box 73, Folder 635)
  - Freshman Year: Scholarship Committee
    See: box 33, folder 290
  - Fri - Fu, 1939-1950 (Box 73, Folder 636)
  - Fund Raising
    See: University Development folders, esp. Report to the President on Procedures for Raising Funds, box 165, folder 1415
  - Furniss, E.S., Provost, 1937-1950 (Box 74, Folder 637)
  - G.I. Bill of Rights
    See: box 136, folder 1135
  - Ga, 1937-1950 (Box 74, Folder 638)
  - Garran, Mr. and Mrs. Francis P., 1937-1946 (Box 74, Folder 639)
  - Ge - Gh, 1937-1950 (Box 74, Folder 640)
  - General Education Board, 1937-1939, 1944-1945 (Box 74, Folder 641)
  - General Studies, Division of, 1937-1942 (Box 74, Folder 642)
  - Generations of Great Teachers (Division of Science), 1946 November 15 (Box 74, Folder 643)
  - Geography, Dept. of, 1945, 1949 (Box 74, Folder 644)
  - Geological Sciences, Dept. of, 1938-1950 (Box 74, Folder 645)
  - Geology: building and oceanographic wing, 1949 (Box 74, Folder 646)
  - Gerasa, 1939 (Box 74, Folder 647)
  - German, Department of, 1938-1950 (Box 75, Folder 648)
    See also: box 147, folder 1240
  - German Scholars, Displaced, 1937-1942 (Box 75, Folder 649)
  - Gi - Gn, 1937-1950 (Box 75, Folder 650)
  - Gibbs, Willard: memorial dinner, 1939 February 11 (Box 75, Folder 651)
  - Gibbs, Willard: New York Hall of Fame, 1950 (Box 75, Folder 652)
  - Glee Club, 1937-1950 (Box 75, Folder 653-655)
  - Glee Club: Yale Opera Project, 1948-1949 (Box 75, Folder 656)
  - Go, 1937-1950 (Box 76, Folder 657-658)
  - Godley, Frederick A.
  - Gosselin, E.N., 1942-1950 (Box 76, Folder 659)
  - Gr, 1938-1950 (Box 76, Folder 660)
  - Graduate School Examination Program
    See: box 33, folder 292
  - Graduate School, 1937-1950 (Box 76, Folder 661-662)
  - Graduate School: scholarships and fellowships, 1937-1950 (Box 76, Folder 663)
  - Graduate Club, 1938-1950 (Box 77, Folder 664)
  - Grants: Problems of Overhead
    See: box 152, folder 1282
  - Graves, Henry S.
    See: box 71, folder 611
  - Graves Committee (Committee on Educational Costs), 1935-1937 (Box 77, Folder 664a)
  - Gre, 1937-1950 (Box 77, Folder 665)
  - Greene, A. Crawford, 1938-1950 (Box 77, Folder 666)
  - Greene, Edward B., 1937-1950 (Box 77, Folder 667)
  - Gregg, Dr. Alan, 1941 (Box 77, Folder 668)
    See also: box 106, folder 904
  - Gri - Gw, 1937-1950 (Box 77, Folder 669)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1938-1941, 1948 (Box 77, Folder 670)
  - Guggenheimer, K.M.
    See: box 155, 1306
  - H, 1937-1950 (Box 77, Folder 671)
  - Hadley, Morris, 1940-1950 (Box 77, Folder 672)
  - Haggard, Dr. Howard, Director, Laboratory of Applied Physiology, 1938-1950 (Box 78, Folder 673)
  - Haggard, Howard W.
    See: boxl 166, folder 1427
  - Hall, Robert A, 1937-1942 (Box 78, Folder 674)
  - Ham - Hap, 1937-1950 (Box 78, Folder 675)
  - Hanes, John W., 1940-1950 (Box 78, Folder 676)
  - Hanna, Howard M., Jr. Fund, 1942-1948 (Box 78, Folder 677)
  - Har, 1937-1950 (Box 78, Folder 678)
  - Harkness, E. S.
    See: box 158, folder 1334-1335
  - Harkness, Mr. and Mrs. Edward S., 1937-1948 (Box 78, Folder 679)
  - Harper, Prof. Fowler
    See: box 96, folder 817